homecashpackage.com 2013-12-23

# Privacy Policy - Home Cash Package

This privacy policy sets out how we will process and use any personal data that you provide to us, or that we may collect as a result of visiting this website. Please read the following information to understand our practices with regards to your personal data and how we will treat it. 

**INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following data about you:  
→ Any information that you provide by filling in forms on our site. This includes provided information at the time of registering to use our site, posting material, requesting further services or subscribing to any service offered by us on the site.   
→ We might also request further information and if you should report a problem with our site.   
→ We may keep a record of any correspondence if you should contact us.   
→ Details of the resources you access and of your visits to our site   
→ Details of transactions you may carry out through our site and of the completion of your orders.   
→ We may collect Name, Address, Phone and Email for marketing purposes with our third party marketing partners. 

**IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES**

We may collect information about your computer; this is statistical data concerning your browsing actions and does not identify you individually. This information includes your IP address where available, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report collective information to our advertisers. 

We may also collect information about your general internet usage using cookie files stored on the hard drive of all computers. The cookies contain valuable information that is transferred to your computers hard drive. In collecting this information we are able to improve our site and deliver a better and more personalised service. 

You can refuse to accept cookies but note that in doing this you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. You can do this by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting. 

Our advertisers may also use cookies but please note that we have no control over this. 

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We reserve the right to disclosure your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, Court order, or legal process served on our Website. 

We use other third Parties such as a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf. When you sign up for our services we will share your information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes. 

If this website is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

From time to time our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you visit any of these sites please note that they have their own privacy policies and you should check these before submitting any personal data. We cannot accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. 

**USE OF DATA COLLECTED**

We use your personal, demographic and profile data to enhance your experience at our site and to enable us to present content we think you might be interested in. We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our site, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, send SMS alerts or notification, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future telemarketing, SMS text-messaging, e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online. By using this site, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section even if your number is found on a do not call registry, in-house list or similar registry. By submitting your information to our website you give us permission to share your information with our third party marketing partners. Our third party marketing partners may contact you via email, telemarketing and direct mail. 

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

This policy may change from time to time. Please visit this page for changes.
